# **SUDIP SUBEDI**

Kathmandu 9851125940 blesssudip@gmail.com

## Snr. Php(Laravel) Developer

## Summary

Enthusiastic web professional motivated by challenging projects and deadlines. Accomplished Back-end developer with extensive experience building Laravel driven websites with frontend Angular Js, HTML5, CSS3 and various web scripting technologies, web standards and project management.

#### Education

2009 - 2012 Bachelor in Computer Application (BCA)

Indira Gandhi Naitonal Open University(IGNOU)

2000 - 2003 Diploma in Electronics Engineering (IE)

Insititute of Engineering, TU

## Work History

Apr 2015 - Present

Snr. PHP(Laravel) Developer

SolutionOneNepal

Developing Software/Web App using Laravel Framework and angular js.

Managing the Development Environment in the Vagrant(Homestead) in Linux/Window System.

Implementing Design Patterns and S.O.L.I.D Principles.

Reviewing the code and performing an adequate level of unit, functional and integrated testing to ensure quality standards are attained.

Participation in process assessment programs and make recommendations to improve software development methods.

Version Control System git implementation.

Mentoring junior developer(s) of the team.

Mar 2014 - Apr 2015 Web Developer

Codeilo

Responsible for building the web sites according to the client requirement.

Transform the client concept to working system.

Software development using the laravel 4.2 framework.

Jun 2011 - Mar 2014 Freelance Web Developer

Freelancing

Working as a freelancer, building the wordpress driven websites using the various web technologies.

Building the custom web applications using core php, javascript, ajax.

Skills —	
Laravel, Lumen	Developed Web app using 4.2, 5, 5.1 versions of laravel.
Angular Js, Cordova	Experienced with building web app using laravel as backend api and angular js as front end.
Wordpress	Experienced in building websites using wordpress.
php, mysql	Experienced developing custom application using core php and mysql.
Jquery, Ajax, Html, Css	Experienced using the given skills html,css, jquery, ajax.
Linux, LAMP, Vagrant	Experienced/Prefer linux, Vagrant, Homestead for development environment.
git, version control system	version control system, github, bitbucket.

### Portfolio -

Some of my projects which i am proud of..

http://sis.abicollege.com - Student Information Management System for the ABI college of UK.

http://misato.ermsys.net/ - Repair Management System for the Japanese misato Company.

http://ermsys.net/yokohama - Repair Management System for the Japanese Yokohoma Company.

http://happyflytravels.com.au/ - Flight/Hotel/Car Booking using amadeus booking api for the Australian Company.